# **Ananda Gharyn**

# Front End Developer

(+62) 8112051201

✓ persolna1243@gmail.com

https://gharynsl123.github.io/

Bekasi, Indonesia

## SUMMARY

I am a software developer specializing in mobile and website development. With 4 years of experience studying at IDN Boarding School, I have successfully completed more than 15 projects. I am now seeking an opportunity to apply my skills in a dynamic software developer role at this company and contribute to its success.

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Partnership with other Companies

03/2023 - 06/2023

Attendance Website SMK Muhammadiyah 2

- · Make a Responsive Website User Interface with Laravel and PHP.
- Collaborated with a diverse team of 3 individuals, leveraging their expertise to deliver high-quality websites that exceeded company expectations.
- · Using an efficient code and resulting good quality. and increased work efficiency, development, and productivity.
- · Using a Middleware to add some protection from data leaks.

Website Project 01/2023 - 06/2023

- Creating a Modern Website with HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, SCSS, and Bootstrap. to increase the front end development
- Using Laravel frameworks, Bootstrap, and many library to create visually appealing and highly functional websites.
- Implemented CRUD middleware, UI Blade Templating, and real-time features to enhance user engagement and improve overall user experience
- Earned lesson for View, Blade, PHP, MySQL DB, Layouting, clean architecture, laravel freamwork.

**Google Cloud Platform** 04/2022 - 06/2023

Google

- · Successfully completed the Backend Management Quiz from Google Cloud.
- · Earned 20 badges for completing all quests.
- Utilized the capabilities of the Google Cloud Platform to enhance data processing, resulting in significant improvements in overall system performance.

Teaching IT Lesson 09/2022 - 09/2022

SMK Rabbaanii Islamic School

- Teaching OOP Java, Android Fundamental, Bootstrap Basic, Database Management System.
- · Inspiring leadership to other people, improve Time management skill.
- Developing social skills to interact with new people and quickly adapt to new environments.

#### Mobile Development Project

04/2022 - 12/2022

- Create an Exquisite Restful API Mobile Experience with Retrofit and RxJava.
- Craft an Aesthetically Pleasing XML View with Enhanced Functionality Using Fragments and Activities.
- Have you created over 20 simple mobile apps and 5 complex mobile apps for Android.
- · Assisting individuals in resolving errors and bugs by providing exceptional solutions

#### EDUCATION

Software Engineer 2024

IDN Boarding School - Vocational High School

- Achieve a top 5 ranking as a participant in the UI/UX Competition organized by the Student Association of the Department of Informatics Engineering at Sultan Agung Islamic University Semarang.
- · Obtained sertifikan Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Android untuk Pemula From dicoding
- · Obtained sertifikan Belajar Dasar Pemrograman Web From dicoding

# CERTIFICATES

**Event UI/UX Competition** 

Responsive Web Design course - Sololearn

Kotlin Course - Sololearn

HTML Course - Sololearn

Learning to Create Android Applications for Beginners - Dicoding

Learning the Basics of Web Programming - Dicoding

**CSS Course - Sololearn** 

# SKILLS

Android	Advanced	PHP	Beginner
Kotlin	Advanced	Rest API	Intermediate
Flutter	Intermediate	MySQL Database	Beginner
Dart	Intermediate	Firebase	Intermediate
HTML	Expert	Team Work	Advanced
CSS	Advanced	Time Management	Advanced
JavaScript	Intermediate	Communication Skills	Intermediate
React JS	Intermediate	Github	Advanced
Bootstrap	Expert	Github Desktop	Intermediate
Laravel	Advanced		

## LANGUAGES

English Fluent Indonesia Native